[Underground of Soul-Cleansing Temple]
Why did you call me back?
Do you know what I was just doing?
Who cares?
Shrimpie appeared just now.
I was waiting for him there.
Do you know what he did?
How would I know?
Stop pretending. You know everything.
You've known all along.
How long are you going to lie to me?
It's been 10 years!
Do you still think
I'm the same as 10 years ago,
doing whatever you tell me to do?
Sit down!
But I won't listen to
another word from you.
Zhang Haixia.
killed everyone in the priest's mansion.
He even hung Priest Su Ya's body
on the water cart
just to avenge us.
Do you know he's completely lost his mind?
Didn't you see him
kill Great Golden Blade?
Didn't you say that no matter what he did,
you'd forgive him,
clean up his mess, and bring him home?
Where is he?
Don't play this game with me.
What does this have to do with
you not telling me the truth?
The antidote Zhang Haixia used
is also a poison.
It will cause irreversible damage
to his mind.
The agents who used this antidote before
all went mad without exception.
They went around attacking people/
They couldn't control themselves at all.
So I killed them all.
He's already saved...
and you're only telling me this now?
Would it have changed anything
if I told you then?
If you knew, would you not have saved him?
Besides, Zhang Haixia
carries clues about Mo Yungao.
It concerns
the safety of countless people.
Even if you didn't choose to do so,
he had to live.
You could have told me earlier.
You and he both hid it from me.
Was it for my own good?
Have you ever considered my feelings?
Well, now you know.
If I asked you to kill him,
could you do it?
Then I have to at least talk to him once.
He might have even shown up just now.
Why on earth did you call me back?
Got me to come back
just to make me clean a darn pond.
Keeping everything from me,
not telling me anything.
Am I not part of the Archives?
Now making me some bullshit Director.
Be it yourself in your coffin.
Priest Su Ya of Bailejing
died of illness previously.
Someone brought him back to life.
But after a few years,
his temperament
suddenly changed drastically.
Originally an honest and gentle man,
he became bloodthirsty.
If the Priest Su Ya's condition
is the same as Zhang Haixia's,
yet he could maintain
his original state for years,
it means he has a way to restrain himself.
Perhaps deep in Bailejing,
there is a way to save Zhang Haixia.
Mentor.
Is it possible that
Priest Su Ya was saved by chief?
Also, if he can cure your illness,
can he also cure Shrimpie?
Maybe.
Don't think about
looking for Zhang Haixia.
He is no longer who he used to be.
If you can't realize this,
then it's best you two don't meet.
He is crazy, not stupid.
He hasn't forgotten us.
Zhang Hailou, think carefully.
Zhang Haixia killed Priest Su Ya
and let you see it,
but didn't come to see you—
why?
He's checking my reaction.
Why did he kill so many people?
Zhang Haixia
is an incredibly smart person.
If he wants to do evil,
even I don't have the confidence
to stop him.
Do you know
how terrifying the person
you have to deal with now is?
You'd better calm down.
Otherwise, just like before,
you'll do something you regret.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 27]
[Soul-Cleansing Temple]
You're back.
I told my sister.
I'm going to kill Mo Yungao
to avenge my family and brothers.
That's up to you.
I will also kill Zhang Haixia.
Is that up to me too?
With the way he is now,
it's hard for anyone to kill him.
If you want to get yourself killed,
I don't mind one more.
Shrimpie.
If you want to play,
I'll play with you.
Little Taoist, you're quite good at this.
Is this how you used to pursue girls?
Why are your ears red?
Don't tell me...
you're still a virgin?
I know you're feeling awful.
I also know
you're like this because you lost
your family and friends.
But you still need to cherish your life
and not hurt yourself.
Or...
their deaths would be in vain.
Darn Taoist,
you're still wet behind the ears!
Stop acting all highly in front of me!
That darn Taoist.
He's obviously experienced nothing
yet preach such big principles.
I need to teach you a lesson.
You're right.
My friends are dead,
and my family is dead too.
Now,
I'm the only one left in this world.
Come and sit down.
My life's so tough I might as well die.
How am I
supposed to live?
Actually,
it's normal to feel pain.
But I'm in too much pain.
I understand.
Drink a little with me.
I...
I know why you want revenge.
It's not for justice,
it's to ease the pain in your heart.
But let me tell you about revenge,
-it isn't...
-Shut up!
What...
What are you doing?
I've taken a fancy to you today.
[Soul-Cleansing Temple]
Robbery.
Robbery?
-I have no money.
-I don’t want your money.
I want this.
You want... manure?
Go.
The dung cart!
My dung cart!
Zhang Hailou, Zhang Hailou.
Wh-Why...
Why are you here?
That's not how
you sounded like last night.
Last night...
What did you give me to drink last night?
Liquor.
Get ready to go.
The women of Phoenix Fortress
are all mantises.
They'll eat you after sleeping with you.
Close your mouth.
Hurry up and pack.
We're leaving for Bone-Washing Cave.
Your mentor and my mentor can't wait.
We are top-tier wanted criminals now.
We need to keep a low profile.
[Soul-Cleansing Temple]
You prepared the crate?
How could you have
predicted everything so precisely?
If you ever get into trouble,
take 3 steps back.
I'll be right behind you
to ensure you have a fallback plan.
No matter what happens,
you'll leave a fallback plan
for me too,
right, Hailou?
[Soul-Cleansing Temple]
Brother!
Let's go look over there!
All right. Don't run!
Brother, this way.
Slowly.
You went crazy the moment you came out.
Why are you still following us?
Didn't I tell you I want revenge?
Since you know Zhang Haixia,
[General Store]
by following you,
I will definitely be able to find him.
You are overthinking it.
He won't follow us anymore.
[Wanted]
Also,
don't expect us to help you
deal with Mo Yungao.
I am trying to save my mentor now
and have no time to deal with him.
I'd like a piece.
Okay, sir.
Did I ask you?
Don't flatter yourself.
Why does Bailejing
have festivals every day?
And different ones too?
Besides, why does everyone
seem to have no reaction
to the death of the priest?
Didn't you hear about
the new priest?
Priest Su Ji took office
-and is now the High Priest of Bailejing.
-The mountain bride is getting married!
-Priest Su Ji...
-Is the younger brother of Priest Su Ya.
-The mountain bride is getting married!
The mountain bride is getting married!
This must be the Bone-Washing Ceremony.
These people are here to wash their bones?
It's the Bone-Washing Ceremony,
yet this kid is shouting about
the mountain bride getting married.
Ma'am.
Aren't people here to wash their bones?
But I just heard someone shouting about
the mountain bride getting married.
They're both happening today.
The marriage and the bone-washing?
Here.
Ma'am.
Why is it you again?
First time strangers, second time friends.
Ma'am, let me ask you,
what are these people doing?
Why are everyone leaving after placing
their bone urns here?
Aren't they supposed to go wash the bones?
People here don't go to wash the bones.
The bridal procession for
the mountain bride will go on our behalf.
On your behalf?
You don't go in person?
In the past,
we would go to wash the bones ourselves.
But this year the priest said
to let the mountain bride's procession
go for us.
The girl to be sent to the mountain
is to be the wife
of our Bailejing's guardian deity,
Feikun Balu.
Letting her wash the bones on our behalf
will allow our loved ones
to rest in peace.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Can I go in together with my mentor
later?
No.
Huh?
Didn't we agree to go to Bone-Washing Cave
to find the chief?
Why can my mentor only go by himself now?
What does this mean?
They are collecting bones now.
The ceremony is later, right?
Scatter first.
Then find a chance to sneak
into the mountain bride's procession.
Thank you.
I'll follow first.
You guys find a chance to sneak in.
I'll follow her first.
Fabrics for sale!
Come and take a look.
Many patterns and pretty styles.
We have all kinds.
This fabric is really good.
Miss, come take a look.
Our new fabrics
will suit you perfectly.
You have great taste, miss.
This fabric suits you very well.
You'll definitely look beautiful in it.
I...
Do you like me?
If I asked you
to take responsibility for me,
would you marry me?
I knew it. You're a hypocrite.
I will!
What did you say?
I said,
I will marry you.
I will take care of you.
I am willing to take responsibility
for you for the rest of my life.
♪ The past fades into traces on the page ♪
The rest of your life?
We've only known each other for a day.
♪ A silent breeze
brushes past that lingering warmth ♪
Besides,
who would marry a
poor Taoist who only lives on a mountain?
I was tricking you.
♪ In this fleeting world,
I long for a moment of vivid life ♪
♪ I may have a chance to open a door ♪
You didn't really think
I liked you, did you?
♪ Where love and wish
meet in a fleeting moment ♪
♪ There's no need to ask questions
in the maze ♪
I'm leaving. Don't follow me.
♪ The world's bustle ♪
♪ Can briefly warm those
under a shared roof ♪
Slowly.
♪ And the story has come to an end ♪
Watch out for the people ahead.
This chief really knows how to enjoy life.
This girl is quite pretty.
What are you looking at?
This is the central stall of the street.
The mountain bride procession
will definitely pass by here.
This one looks quite nice.
It should—
Do you really think
we're here for shopping?
It should suit me.
Why don't you help me put it on?
I can't beat him up in the street.
Done.
All right.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
Want some barbecue?
That's my disciple.
My disciple.
I taught him well.
All right.
Have a taste.
Have one?
It's good.
Why does this bride's wedding dress
look so familiar?
[Yue Shu, the bride]
Wanduo?
So Wanduo is going to be
the mountain bride.
What's the deal with the mountain bride?
Why turn them into something like this?
Hey!
Miss, this doesn't feel right.
Save me!
The bride is being snatched!
Somebody come quick!
Hurry!
The bride has been snatched away!
What did you do?
We haven't even been here
for even an hour.
I didn't do anything.
All I did was act a little vain
and put on a silver accessory.
Hurry!
Quick!
Let's go!
Sir,
did you see two men
looking like they were running away?
What?
He's asking you
if you have you seen two men—
one looking like a Taoist priest
and one pretty boy?
Nope, didn't see them.
I'm busy.
Go away.
Did they go to the other side?
We can't cross with weapons.
This side of the river
is called Balianjie.
The authorities
on both sides don't get along.
They are carrying swords,
so they definitely wouldn't dare go there.
Why don't we...
go hide on the other side of the river?
Let's go.
If we
stay here,
can Feng Huang and Madam find us?
My mentor gets away quickly.
Anyway, we have to
meet up at Bone-Washing Cave.
We shouldn't worry too much.
What's the deal with that bride?
Do you know her?
No.
It was after seeing my tattoo
that she stopped to ask me for help.
What tattoo?
My tattoo is quite special.
It's right here.
The girl recognized it at a glance
and asked for help.
It means she is very familiar with us.
You are also from the Zhang family.
Do you know much about the chief?
What about?
The chief
has a similar tattoo
right here.
We are newcomers here.
If the people here know about this tattoo,
the chief must have told them.
But why would the chief tell someone
about this tattoo for no reason?
Their relationship must be
beyond ordinary.
Or perhaps,
she saw the tattoo, and he had to
explain it to her.
See, that relationship
is even more unusual.
He must have said it
when they were going at it.
Going at what?
Consummation.
What are you saying?
How could the chief
be that kind of person?
Do you know him well?
This chief,
I heard he is apathetic.
Let alone romance,
he barely even eats.
He has an eccentric temperament—
who'd have thought?
After moving to Nanqiang
to live in seclusion,
he would actually...
talk to someone about his tattoo?
But this place is quite lively,
and that girl is absolutely gorgeous.
The chief sure has good taste.
He acts like a wild man.
The most outrageous thing
she asked for my help
when she was
on her way to getting married.
What does this mean?
It means it wasn't the chief
she was getting married to.
It seems there's something up
with Feikun Balu.
Whatever.
Since she's the chief's woman,
she must be protected.
She should have clues
about the chief.
We can also take the chance to figure out,
what this mountain bride is all about.
Let's go.
I have no money to pay the bill.
You're out of money?
Let's go.
Sir.
Have you seen two men?
One looks like a Taoist priest,
the other a pretty boy?
No, no.
Go ask someone else.
Let's go.
Sir.
Have you seen
an outsider with a beast tattoo?
A tattoo right here.
What about him?